A Guide to the Papers of Henry Heth, 1765-1800
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Letter from William M. Heth to Harry Heth 1815 Jun 12 (Box 9)
- Letter from Robert Perkins to Harry Heth 1815 Jun 15 (Box 9)
- Letter from Beverly Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 Jun 13 (Box 9)
- Letter from John Tayloe to Harry Heth 1815 Jun 14 (Box 9)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Beverly Randolph 1815 Jun 15 (Box 9)
- Letter from John Potts to Harry Heth 1815 Jun 15 (Box 9)
- Letter from Oliver Evans to Harry Heth 1815 Jun 20 (Box 9)
- Letter from Beverly Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 Jun 22 (Box 9)
- Letter from John D. Blair to Harry Heth 1815 Jun 22 (Box 9)
- Letter from D. M. Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 Jun 22 (Box 9)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Beverly Randolph 1815 Jun 27 (Box 9)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Henry Heth 1815 Jun 29 (Box 9)
- Letter from Robert Pleasants to Harry Heth 1815 Jun 30 (Box 9)
- Letter from Beverly Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 Jul 3 (Box 9)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Beverly Randolph 1815 Jul 5 (Box 9)
- Letter from Beverly Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 Jul 10 (Box 9)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Beverly Randolph 1815 Jul 14 (Box 9)
- Letter from H. Heth to Henry Heth 1815 Jul 14 (Box 9)
- Letter from Beverly Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 Jul 15 (Box 9)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1815 Jul 15 (Box 9)
- Letter from Andrew Ramsey to Harry Heth 1815 Jul 16 (Box 9)
- Letter from William Bolling 1815 Jul 16 (Box 9)
- Letter from Richard Hughes to Harry Heth 1815 Jul 19 (Box 9)
- Letter from Robert Hughes to Harry Heth 1815 Jul 20 (Box 9)
- Letter from Thomas Mann Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 Jul 22 (Box 9)
- Letter from A. Stewart to Harry Heth 1815 Jul 23 (Box 9)
- Letter from M. K. Murray to Harry Heth 1815 Jul 24 (Box 9)
- Letter from John Potts to Harry Heth 1815 Jul 25 (Box 9)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1815 Jul 25 (Box 9)
- Letter from James Myers to Harry Heth 1815 Jul 27 (Box 9)
- Letter from Robert Hughes to Harry Heth 1815 Jul 28 (Box 9)
- Letter from Robert Hughes to Harry Heth 1815 Jul 28 (Box 9)
- Letter from John Potts to Harry Heth 1815 Jul 28 (Box 9)
- Letter from John Potts to Harry Heth 1815 Jul 28 (Box 9)
- Letter from Robert Hughes to Harry Heth 1815 Jul 29 (Box 9)
- Letter from James Myers to Harry Heth 1815 Jul 29 (Box 9)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Beverly Randolph 1815 Jul 30 (Box 9)
- Letter from D. M. Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 Jul 31 (Box 9)
- Letter from Randolph Harrison to Harry Heth 1815 Jul 31 (Box 9)
- Letter from Thomas Railey to Harry Heth 1815 Aug 1 (Box 9)
- Letter from James C. Harris to Harry Heth 1815 Aug 2 (Box 9)
- Letter from William Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 Aug 3 (Box 9)
- Letter from William Bolling to Harry Heth 1815 Aug 4 (Box 9)
- Letter from John Tayloe to Harry Heth 1815 Aug 5 (Box 9)
- Letter from William Chandler to Harry Heth 1815 Aug 6 (Box 9)
- Letter from Beverly Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 Aug 7 (Box 9)
- Letter from John R. Triplett to Harry Heth 1815 Aug 7 (Box 9)
- Letter from Randolph Harrison to Harry Heth 1815 Aug 7 (Box 9)
- Letter from Robert Hughes to Harry Heth 1815 Aug 8 (Box 9)
- Letter from Jonah Smith to Harry Heth (Box 9)
- Letter from James Myers to Harry Heth 1815 Aug 10 (Box 9)
- Letter from James Hean to Harry Heth 1815 Aug 10 (Box 9)
- Letter from Harry Heth to James E. Harris 1815 Aug 11 (Box 9)
- Letter from Richard T. Hackley to Harry Heth 1815 Aug 15 (Box 9)
- Letter from William Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 Aug 15 (Box 9)
- Letter from Levin Coit to Harry Heth 1815 Aug 16 (Box 9)
- Letter from Thomas Eston Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 Aug 16 (Box 9)
- Letter from James Myers to Harry Heth 1815 Aug 19 (Box 9)
- Letter from James E. Harris to Harry Heth 1815 Aug 17 (Box 9)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Beverly Randolph 1815 Aug 20 (Box 9)
- Letter from Thomas Ramsey to Harry Heth 1815 Aug 20 (Box 9)
- Letter from Beverly Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 Aug 22 (Box 9)
- Letter from Barbara Bloome to [?] 1815 Aug 23 (Box 9)
- Letter from Andrew Ramsey to Harry Heth 1815 Aug 23 (Box 9)
- Letter from William McGuire to Harry Heth 1815 Aug 23 (Box 9)
- Letter from James Myers to Harry Heth 1815 Aug 24 (Box 9)
- Letter from Robert Hughes to Harry Heth 1815 Aug 26 (Box 9)
- Letter from James Myers to Harry Heth 1815 Aug 25 (Box 9)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Beverly Randolph 1815 Aug 30 (Box 9)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Beverly Randolph 1815 Sep 5 (Box 9)
- Letter from William Chandler to Harry Heth 1815 Sep 7 (Box 9)
- Letter from H. Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 Sep 10 (Box 9)
- Letter from C. & R. Railey to Harry Heth 1815 Sep 12 (Box 9)
- Letter from P. A. Sabbaton to Harry Heth 1815 Sep 12 (Box 9)
- Letter from Robert Pleasants to Harry Heth 1815 Sep 12 (Box 9)
- Letter from Samuel Myers to Harry Heth 1815 Sep 12 (Box 9)
- Letter from Robert Taylor to Harry Heth 1815 Sep 16 (Box 9)
- Letter from Thomas Mann Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 Sep 17 (Box 9)
- Letter from [?] to Harry Heth 1815 Sep 17 (Box 10)
- Letter from Robert Perkins to Harry Heth 1815 Sep 18 (Box 10)
- Letter from Beverly Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 Sep 19 (Box 10)
- Letter from N. Ellicott to Harry Heth 1815 Sep 22 (Box 10)
- Letter from Richard Young to Harry Heth 1815 Sep 24 (Box 10)
- Letter from William Sharp to Harry Heth 1815 Sep 26 (Box 10)
- Letter from John Boyster to Harry Heth 1815 Sep 26 (Box 10)
- Letter from Beverly Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 Sep 26 (Box 10)
- Letter from Richard Young to Isaac Webster 1815 Sep 28 (Box 10)
- Letter from Robert Hughes to Isaac Webster 1815 Sep 28 (Box 10)
- Letter from P. A. Sabbaton to Isaac Webster 1815 Sep 29 (Box 10)
- Letter from Robert Hughes to Harry Heth 1815 Sep 30 (Box 10)
- Letter from John Potts to Harry Heth 1815 Oct (Box 10)
- Letter from Thomas Mann Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 4 (Box 10)
- Letter from Robert B. Taylor to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 4 (Box 10)
- Letter from R. Hughes to [?] 1815 Oct 4 (Box 10)
- Letter from Robert Porterfield to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 5 (Box 10)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Richard Hughes 1815 Oct 6 (Box 10)
- Letter from Robert Hughes to [?] 1815 Oct 6 (Box 10)
- Letter from John Potts to [?] 1815 Oct 6 (Box 10)
- Letter from John Tandy to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 7 (Box 10)
- Letter from John Potts to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 7 (Box 10)
- Letter from D. Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 9 (Box 10)
- Letter from Richard Young to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 9 (Box 10)
- Letter from Harry Heth to John Davidson 1815 Oct 9 (Box 10)
- Letter from R. Hughes to John Potts 1815 Oct 9 (Box 10)
- Letter from R. Hughes to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 9 (Box 10)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Thomas Railey & brother 1815 Oct 10 (Box 10)
- Letter from Ben Huppard to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 10 (Box 10)
- Letter from R. Hughes to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 11 (Box 10)
- Letter from John Davidson to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 13 (Box 10)
- Letter from W. Anderson to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 14 (Box 10)
- Letter from R. Hughes to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 16 (Box 10)
- Letter from Beverly Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 16 (Box 10)
- Letter from John Potts to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 16 (Box 10)
- Letter from Worthern & McGrinder to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 17 (Box 10)
- Letter from John Potts to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 17 (Box 10)
- Letter from John Potts to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 17 (Box 10)
- Letter from William Robertson to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 18 (Box 10)
- Letter from Ben Huppard to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 19 (Box 10)
- Letter from Robert Perkins to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 19 (Box 10)
- Letter from R. Hughes to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 19 (Box 10)
- Letter from James C. Anthony to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 20 (Box 10)
- Letter from Daniel Garland to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 21 (Box 10)
- Letter from Harry Heth to D. M. Randolph 1815 Oct 22 (Box 10)
- Letter from Nat. Ellicott to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 24 (Box 10)
- Letter from R. Hughes to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 24 (Box 10)
- Letter from Beverly Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 24 (Box 10)
- Letter from John Potts to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 24 (Box 10)
- Letter from R. Hughes to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 26 (Box 10)
- Letter from D. M. & R. Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 27 (Box 10)
- Letter from Jordan Martin to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 29 (Box 10)
- Letter from Thomas Strade to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 31 (Box 10)
- Letter from Beverly Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 31 (Box 10)
- Letter from Richard Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 Oct 31 (Box 10)
- Letter from Thomas Mann Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 Dec 4 (Box 10)
- Letter from H. Heth to Henry Heth 1815 Nov 1 (Box 10)
- Letter from Henry Banks to Harry Heth 1815 Nov 3 (Box 10)
- Letter from H. G. Heth to Harry Heth 1815 Nov 5 (Box 10)
- Letter from John Potts to Harry Heth 1815 Nov 5 (Box 10)
- Letter from Peter Rowley to Harry Heth 1815 Nov 6 (Box 10)
- Letter from Gabriel Peterson to Harry Heth 1815 Nov 12 (Box 10)
- Letter from William Mayo to Harry Heth 1815 Nov 12 (Box 10)
- Letter from William Randolph to Harry Heth 1815 Nov 13 (Box 10)
- Letter from John Heth to Harry Heth 1815 Nov 14 (Box 10)
- Letter from R. Hughes to Harry Heth 1815 Nov 18 (Box 10)
- Letter from Henry Banks to Harry Heth 1815 Nov 19 (Box 10)
- Letter from John Harris to Harry Heth 1815 Nov 21 (Box 10)
- Letter from Robert Porterfield to Harry Heth 1815 Nov 25 (Box 10)
- Letter from Robert Perkins to Harry Heth 1815 Nov 25 (Box 10)
- Letter from Henry Heth to Harry Heth 1815 Nov 29 (Box 10)
- Letter from Harry Heth to John Harris 1815 Nov 29 (Box 10)
- Letter from Thomas L. Booth to Harry Heth 1815 Nov 30 (Box 10)
- Letter from Peter F. Smith to Harry Heth 1815 Nov 30 (Box 10)
- Letter from Henry Banks to Harry Heth 1815 Dec 3 (Box 10)
- Letter from Ben Sheppard to Harry Heth 1815 Dec 5 (Box 10)
- Letter from John Chowning to Harry Heth 1815 Dec 6 (Box 10)
- Memorandum of articles of copartnary between Robert Gordon, Harry Heth, James Currie, & Benjamin Sheppard 1815 Dec 9 (Box 10)
- Letter from William Barksdale to [?] 1815 Dec 10 (Box 10)
- Letter from H. Lawrence to Harry Heth 1815 Dec 12 (Box 10)
- Letter from Dabney Browne to Harry Heth 1815 Dec 12 (Box 10)
- Letter from John Tanay to Harry Heth 1815 Dec 13 (Box 10)
- Letter from Benjamin Sheppard to Harry Heth 1815 Dec 13 (Box 10)
- Letter from Robert B. Gaines to Harry Heth 1815 Dec 20 (Box 10)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1815 Dec 23 (Box 10)
- Power of attorney - Francis Pureer to Dabney Browne 1815 Dec 27 (Box 10)
- Letter from John Potts to Harry Heth 1815 Dec 28 (Box 10)
- Memorandum of agreement between Harry Heth & Thomas Bailey 1815 (Box 10)
- Agreement between Joseph Marx and Heth and Randolph 1816 Jan 1 (Box 10)
- Accounts and receipts for 1815 1815 (Box 10)
- Letter from John Browne, Jr., to Harry Heth 1816 Jan 12 (Box 10)
- Letter from Thomas Railey to Harry Heth 1816 Jan 12 (Box 10)
- Letter from [?] to Harry Heth 1816 Jan 30 (Box 10)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1816 Feb 1 (Box 10)
- Memorandum between Harry Heth & David Street 1816 Feb 6 (Box 10)
- Letter from H. G. Heth to Harry Heth 1816 Mar 12 (Box 10)
- Agreement between Harry Heth & Abram Wooldridge 1816 Apr 6 (Box 10)
- Letter from Norborne Chandler to Harry Heth 1816 Apr 9 (Box 10)
- Letter from William Barksdale to Harry Heth 1816 Jun 5 (Box 10)
- Letter from John Crease to Harry Heth 1815 Jun 26 (Box 10)
- Letter from Mr. McQueene to Harry Heth 1816 Aug 3 (Box 10)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Thomas Railey & brother 1816 Aug 11 (Box 10)
- Letter from David G. Ogden to Harry Heth 1816 Oct 2 (Box 10)
- Letter from Carter Page to Harry Heth 1816 Nov 16 (Box 10)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Beverly Randolph 1816 Nov 17 (Box 10)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Thomas Railey & brother 1816 Oct 17 (Box 10)
- Letter from Thomas B. Main to Harry Heth 1816 Dec 2 (Box 10)
- Letter from George Meigis to Harry Heth 1816 Dec 26 (Box 10)
- Letter from Joseph Wheaton to Harry Heth 1816 Dec 2 (Box 10)
- Letter from D. Randolph to Harry Heth 1816 Dec 13 (Box 10)
- Letter from Anderson Salle to Harry Heth 1816 Dec 15 (Box 10)
- Letter from D. M. Railey to Harry Heth 1816 Dec 31 (Box 10)
- Accounts and receipts for 1816 1816 (Box 10)
- Letter from M. Trabue to Harry Heth 1817 Jan 3 (Box 10)
- Letter from Robert Perkins to Harry Heth 1817 Jan 8 (Box 10)
- Letter from D. Randolph to Harry Heth 1817 Jan 11 (Box 10)
- Letter from Robert Pleasants to Harry Heth 1817 Jan 13 (Box 10)
- Letter from [?] to Harry Heth 1817 Jan 11 (Box 10)
- Letter from Harry Heth to John Ashton 1817 Jan 11 (Box 10)
- Letter from William F. Carter to Harry Heth 1817 Jan 17 (Box 10)
- Letter from William G. Bowis to [?] 1817 Jan 17 (Box 10)
- Letter from Harry Heth to [?] 1817 Jan 17 (Box 10)
- Letter from William Hundley to Harry Heth 1817 Jan 18 (Box 10)
- Letter from William Carter to Beverly Randolph 1817 Jan 19 (Box 10)
- Letter from W. Bolling to Harry Heth 1817 Jan 20 (Box 10)
- Letter from Beverly Randolph to Harry Heth 1817 Jan 20 (Box 11)
- Letter from William F. Carter to Beverly Randolph 1817 Jan 26 (Box 11)
- Letter from Ben Sheppard to Harry Heth 1817 Jan 25 (Box 11)
- Letter from Ben Sheppard to Harry Heth 1817 Jan 26 (Box 11)
- Letter from John Stewart to Harry Heth 1817 Jan 31 (Box 11)
- Letter from William F. Carter to Beverly Randolph 1817 Jan 31 (Box 11)
- Letter from L. Turner to Harry Heth 1817 Feb 2 (Box 11)
- Letter from Dan Mayo Railey to Harry Heth 1817 Feb 8 (Box 11)
- Letter from R. B. Taylor to Harry Heth 1817 Feb 10 (Box 11)
- Bond-Rebecca Harris & CorbinMcRae 1817 Feb 10 (Box 11)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1817 Feb 16 (Box 11)
- Letter from John H. Crease to Harry Heth 1817 Feb 11 (Box 11)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1817 Feb 13 (Box 11)
- Letter from Robert Perkins to Harry Heth 1817 Feb 14 (Box 11)
- Letter from A. M. Harrison to Harry Heth 1817 Feb 18 (Box 11)
- Letter from Andrew Ramsey to Harry Heth 1817 Feb 23 (Box 11)
- Letter from J. H. Chew to Harry Heth 1817 Feb 25 (Box 11)
- Letter from John H. Crease to Harry Heth 1817 Feb 26 (Box 11)
- Letter from Robert Young to Harry Heth 1817 Mar 5 (Box 11)
- Letter from A. Wooldridge to [?] 1817 Mar 5 (Box 11)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Robert Young 1817 Mar 6 (Box 11)
- Letter from B. M. Carter to Beverly Randolph 1817 Mar 6 (Box 11)
- Letter from William F. Carter to Beverly Randolph 1817 Mar 7 (Box 11)
- Letter from W. G. Warner to Harry Heth 1817 Mar 9 (Box 11)
- Letter from W. G. Warner to Harry Heth 1817 Mar 7 (Box 11)
- Letter from B. Sheppard to Harry Heth 1817 Mar 7 (Box 11)
- Letter from R. Ryland Randolph to Harry Heth 1817 Mar 9 (Box 11)
- Letter from Dan Mayo Railey to Harry Heth 1817 Mar 10 (Box 11)
- Letter from John Stewart to Harry Heth 1817 Mar 12 (Box 11)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1817 Mar 15 (Box 11)
- Letter from George Meigis to Harry Heth 1817 Mar 15 (Box 11)
- Letter from Ben Sheppard to Harry Heth 1817 Mar 17 (Box 11)
- Letter from Ben Sheppard to Harry Heth 1817 Mar 20 (Box 11)
- Letter from W. G. Povall to Harry Heth 1817 Mar 22 (Box 11)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1817 Mar 27 (Box 11)
- Letter from William F. Carter to Beverly Randolph 1817 Apr 9 (Box 11)
- Letter from John Mason to Harry Heth 1817 Apr 9 (Box 11)
- Letter from F. Maury to [?] 1817 Apr 7 (Box 11)
- Letter from Hugh Mercer to Harry Heth & Beverly Randolph 1817 Apr 16 (Box 11)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1817 Apr 19 (Box 11)
- Letter from John Heth to Harry Heth 1817 Apr 16 (Box 11)
- Letter from Hugh Mercer to Harry Heth 1817 Apr 16 (Box 11)
- Letter from William F. Carter to Beverly Randolph 1817 Apr 17 (Box 11)
- Letter from Charles Wayman to Harry Heth 1817 Apr 21 (Box 11)
- Letter from Hugh Mercer to Heth & Randolph 1817 Apr 22 (Box 11)
- Letter from John Mason to Heth & Randolph 1817 Apr 23 (Box 11)
- Letter from R. Hughes to Harry Heth 1817 Apr 24 (Box 11)
- Letter from B. Sheppard to Harry Heth 1817 Apr 24 (Box 11)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1817 Apr 25 (Box 11)
- Letter from George Mason to Harry Heth 1817 Apr 27 (Box 11)
- Letter from Joseph Wheaton to Harry Heth 1817 Apr 29 (Box 11)
- Letter from William Randolph to Harry Heth 1817 Apr 30 (Box 11)
- Letter from Charles Wayman to Harry Heth 1817 May 2 (Box 11)
- Letter from Kitty Stewart to Harry Heth 1817 May 2 (Box 11)
- Letter from Samuel Farnandis to Harry Heth 1817 May 13 (Box 11)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1817 May 14 (Box 11)
- Letter from C. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1817 May 15 (Box 11)
- Letter from Charles Wayman to Harry Heth 1817 May 16 (Box 11)
- Letter from R. Hughes to Harry Heth 1817 May 17 (Box 11)
- Letter from Thomas Railey & Brother to Harry Heth 1817 May 19 (Box 11)
- Letter from Dan Mayo Railey to Harry Heth 1817 May 21 (Box 11)
- Letter from Charles Wayman to Harry Heth 1817 May 24 (Box 11)
- Letter from C. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1817 May 27 (Box 11)
- Letter from John Tandy to Harry Heth 1817 May 27 (Box 11)
- Letter from E. Merger to Harry Heth 1817 Jun 4 (Box 11)
- Agreement between B. M. Carter & Beverly Randolph 1817 Jun 5 (Box 11)
- Letter from Charles Wayman to Harry Heth 1817 Jun 11 (Box 11)
- Letter from Henry G. Heth to Harry Heth 1817 Jun 13 (Box 11)
- Agreement-Heth, T. Plunt, John Tanabue, P. M. Cory, Thomas Proctor, & Samuel Woody 1817 Jun 14 (Box 11)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Thomas Railey & Brother 1817 Jun 16 (Box 11)
- Letter from Harry Heth to T. Martin 1817 Jun 19 (Box 11)
- Letter from William Randolph to Harry Heth 1817 Jun 23 (Box 11)
- Letter from Hugh Mercer to Beverly Randolph 1817 Jun 26 (Box 11)
- Letter from William Randolph to Harry Heth 1817 Jun 27 (Box 11)
- Letter from Joseph Lovelle to Beverly Randolph 1817 Jul 7 (Box 11)
- Letter from Jordan Martin to Harry Heth 1817 Jul 9 (Box 11)
- Letter from James Keeler to Harry Heth 1817 Jul 14 (Box 11)
- Letter from Hugh Mercer to Harry Heth 1817 Jul 17 (Box 11)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Mssrs. Cundiffe, Nabue, Blunt, Cary, Porter, & Woody 1817 Jul 22 (Box 11)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1817 Jul 23 (Box 11)
- Letter from E. Landrum to Harry Heth 1817 Jul 29 (Box 11)
- Letter from H. Chew to Harry Heth 1817 Aug 3 (Box 11)
- Letter from Joseph Wheaton to Harry Heth 1817 Aug 5 (Box 11)
- Letter from [?] to Samuel G. Adams 1817 Aug 9 (Box 11)
- Letter from James E. Harris to Harry Heth 1817 Sep 3 (Box 11)
- Letter from John Scott to [?] 1817 Sep 13 (Box 11)
- Letter from Ben Sheppard to Harry Heth 1817 Sep 23 (Box 11)
- Letter from B. Randolph to James Vass 1817 Sep 29 (Box 11)
- Letter from A. Caton to Harry Heth 1817 Sep 30 (Box 11)
- Letter from Philip Woodson to Harry Heth 1817 Oct 3 (Box 11)
- Letter from Francis Corbin to Harry Heth 1817 Oct 7 (Box 11)
- Letter from C. H. Drew to Harry Heth 1817 Oct 12 (Box 11)
- Letter from William Randolph to Harry Heth 1817 Oct 12 (Box 11)
- Letter from John Potts to [?] 1817 Dec 17 (Box 11)
- Letter from P. E. Tabb to Harry Heth 1817 Oct 17 (Box 11)
- Letter from Jacob Klein to Harry Heth 1817 Oct 18 (Box 11)
- Letter from James & John Dunlop to Harry Heth 1817 Oct 20 (Box 11)
- Letter from George Mayes to Harry Heth 1817 Oct 26 (Box 11)
- Letter from William Randolph to Harry Heth 1817 Oct 30 (Box 11)
- Deed-Claiborne Mayes 1817 Nov 3 (Box 11)
- Letter from Harry Heth to [?] 1817 Nov 5 (Box 11)
- Letter from Harry Heth to [?] 1815 Nov 5 (Box 11)
- Letter from J. Mann to Harry Heth 1817 Nov 16 (Box 11)
- Letter from A. M. Harrison to Harry Heth 1817 Nov 17 (Box 11)
- Letter from Francis Follet to Harry Heth 1817 Nov 17 (Box 11)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Francis Follet 1817 Nov 17 (Box 11)
- Letter from Jacob Klein to Harry Heth 1817 Nov 21 (Box 11)
- Letter from John Lanay to Harry Heth 1817 Nov 2 (Box 11)
- Letter from John Bell to Harry Heth 1817 Nov 26 (Box 11)
- Letter from R. Hughes to Harry Heth 1817 Nov 30 (Box 11)
- Letter from William Martin to Harry Heth 1817 Dec 2 (Box 11)
- Letter from Robert Pleasants to Harry Heth 1817 Dec 4 (Box 11)
- Letter from Thomas Railey & Brother to Harry Heth 1817 Dec 9 (Box 11)
- Letter from John B. Taylor to Harry Heth 1817 Dec 15 (Box 11)
- Letter from John B. Taylor to Harry Heth 1817 Dec 17 (Box 11)
- Letter from W. C. Bowyer to Harry Heth 1817 Dec 20 (Box 11)
- Letter from Andrew Ramsey to Harry Heth 1817 Dec 23 (Box 11)
- Letter from Robert Pleasants to Harry Heth 1817 Dec 27 (Box 11)
- Letter from Harry Heth to A. S. Wooldridge 1817 Dec 28 (Box 11)
- Accounts and receipts for 1817 1817 (Box 11)
- Letter from [?] to Mssrs. Yateses & Co. 1818 (Box 11)
- Letter from Robert Young to Harry Heth 1818 Jan (Box 11)
- Letter from P. G. Tabb to Harry Heth 1818 Jan 8 (Box 11)
- Letter from Thomas Railey & Brother to Harry Heth 1818 Jan 18 (Box 11)
- Letter from Charles Railey to Harry Heth 1818 Feb 8 (Box 11)
- Letter from Henry Heth to Harry Heth 1818 Feb 24 (Box 11)
- Letter from William B. Giles to Harry Heth 1818 May 28 (Box 11)
- Letter from James Brown, Jr., to Harry Heth 1818 Jun 4 (Box 11)
- Letter from W. C. Bowyer to Harry Heth 1818 Jun 14 (Box 11)
- Memorandum between M. Bryson & M. Sampson 1818 Jul 2 (Box 11)
- Memorandum re steam engine 1818 Jul 2 (Box 11)
- Letter from J. H. Hurst to Harry Heth 1818 Jul 10 (Box 11)
- Letter from W. S. Stone to Harry Heth 1818 Aug 18 (Box 11)
- Letter from S. Betten to Harry Heth 1818 Aug 27 (Box 12)
- Letter from Dan M. Railey to Harry Heth 1818 Sep 21 (Box 12)
- Letter from William M. Heth to Harry Heth 1818 Sep 30 (Box 12)
- Letter from Elizabeth Farrar to Harry Heth 1818 Oct 6 (Box 12)
- Letter from Robert McQueen & Co. to Harry Heth 1818 Nov 21 (Box 12)
- Letter from Frank B. Ogden to Mssrs. Fenton, Murray, & Wood 1818 Nov 26 (Box 12)
- Letter from Frank Ogden to Harry Heth 1818 Nov 30 (Box 12)
- Letter from Harry Heth to Mssrs. Fontaine, Murray, & Woods 1818 Dec 8 (Box 12)
- Agreement between Harry Heth and James and John Baird 1818 Dec 8 (Box 12)
- Letter from John Taliaferro to Harry Heth 1818 Dec 11 (Box 12)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1818 Dec 12 (Box 12)
- Letter from J. M. Mason to [?] 1818 Dec 30 (Box 12)
- Letter from Henry Banks to Harry Heth 1818 Dec 31 (Box 12)
- Accounts and receipts for 1818 1818 (Box 12)
- Letter from Thomas Mann Randolph to Harry Heth 1819 Jan 3 (Box 12)
- Letter from N. Ellicott to Harry Heth 1819 Jan 6 (Box 12)
- Letter from R. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1819 Jan 8 (Box 12)
- Letter from Harry Heth to David Street 1819 Jan 12 (Box 12)
- Letter from Robert Pleasants to Harry Heth 1812 Jan 18 (Box 12)
- Letter from W. L. Stone to Harry Heth 1819 Jan 20 (Box 12)
- Court Permission to Harry Heth to build a canal 1819 Jan 20 (Box 12)
- Letter from R. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1819 Jan 21 (Box 12)
- Letter from Francis L. Taylor to Harry Heth 1819 Jan 23 (Box 12)
- Agreement of James M. Harris 1819 Jan 23 (Box 12)
- Letter from J. P. Pleasants to Harry Heth 1819 Jan 27 (Box 12)
- Letter from Samuel Winchester to Harry Heth 1819 Feb 2 (Box 12)
- Letter from R. Railey to Harry Heth 1819 Feb 2 (Box 12)
- Letter from Fenton, Murray, & Wood to Harry Heth 1819 Feb 2 (Box 12)
- Letter from W. B. Pillsborough to Harry Heth 1819 Feb 6 (Box 12)
- Letter from John Browne to [?] 1819 Feb 9 (Box 12)
- Letter from H. Hackley to Harry Heth 1819 Feb 11 (Box 12)
- Letter from A. M. Harrison to Harry Heth 1819 Feb 14 (Box 12)
- Letter from W. D. [?] to Harry Heth 1819 Feb 15 (Box 12)
- Letter from William S. Dance to [?] 1819 Feb 16 (Box 12)
- Letter from Sam Christian to Harry Heth 1819 Feb 17 (Box 12)
- Letter from Samuel Taylor to Harry Heth 1819 Feb 19 (Box 12)
- Letter from Samuel Taylor to Harry Heth 1819 Feb 19 (Box 12)
- Letter from Sam Winchester to Harry Heth 1819 Feb 25 (Box 12)
- Letter from Robert Perkins to [?] 1819 Feb 28 (Box 12)
- Letter from H. B. Christian to Harry Heth 1819 Mar 1 (Box 12)
- Letter from Andrew Ramsay to Harry Heth 1819 Mar 7 (Box 12)
- Letter from James Woody to Harry Heth 1819 Mar 10 (Box 12)
- Letter from Robert Mackay to Harry Heth 1819 Mar 1 (Box 12)